<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="fortune_list">
        <item>The end is near and it is all your fault</item>
        <item>meh.</item>
        <item>Only listen to fortune cookie, disregard all other fortune telling units</item>
        <item>Confucius says: Go to bed with an itchy bum, wake up with a stinky finger</item>
        <item>Hearty laughter is a good way to jog internally without having to go outdoors</item>
        <item>You will die alone and poorly dressed</item>
        <item>A new pair of shoes will do you a world of good</item>
        <item>Now it is time to make circles with mints, do not haste any longer</item>
        <item>Help! I am being held prisoner inside this android phone!</item>
        <item>The fortune you seek will come with another glass of juice</item>
        <item>Marriage lets you annoy one special person for rest of your life</item>
        <item>Fortune says, a palm can say a lot, especially when it smacks</item>
        <item>Today is probably a huge improvement over yesterday</item>
        <item>Every exit is an entrance to new exit. Except the one in this office. It merely stinks</item>
        <item>You can\'t be trusted to keep a secret</item>
        <item>Confucius says: If you think we\'re going to sum up your life in this tiny message, you are crazy!</item>
        <item>You will receive a fortune (message)</item>
        <item>Someone has googled you recently</item>
        <item>You will be hungry again in one hour</item>
        <item>Don\'t drink any juice today, you will be very sick</item>
        <item>How much deeper would be ocean be without sponges</item>
        <item>You will read this and say "Geez, I could come up with better fortunes than that"</item>
        <item>That ain\'t juice</item>
        <item>You are not illliterate</item>
        <item>An alien of some sort will be appearing to you shortly</item>
        <item>Get a life</item>
        <item>404 Fortune not found</item>
        <item>Keep your goals away from the trolls</item>
        <item>The stories you touch today, will be stuck, like, forever!</item>
        <item>For a change you will code today</item>
        <item>You know that code isn\'t going to write itself. Stop drinking free juice and get back</item>
        <item>When you squeeze orange, orange juice comes out; because that\'s what\'s inside</item>
        <item>A conclusion is simply the place where you got tired of thinking</item>
        <item>A cynic is only a frustrated optimist</item>
        <item>Flattery will go far tonight</item>
        <item>A starship ride has been promised to you by the galactic wizard</item>
        <item>A tub and a rub will change your day</item>
        <item>Because of your melodic nature, the moonlight never misses an appointment</item>
        <item>Confucius say you have heart as big as this glass of juice</item>
        <item>It\’s about time I got displayed as a fortune</item>
        <item>Never forget a friend. Especially if he owes you</item>
        <item>Never wear your best pants when you go to fight for freedom</item>
        <item>There is no mistake so great as that of being always right</item>
        <item>You will gain admiration from your peers</item>
        <item>Accept that some days you’re the pigeon, and some days you’re the statue</item>
        <item>Don\'t sweat the petty things and don\'t pet the sweaty things</item>
        <item>If opportunity doesn\'t knock, build a door</item>
        <item>When everything’s coming your way, you’re in the wrong lane</item>
        <item>Two days from now, tomorrow will be yesterday</item>
        <item> Your inferiority complex not good enough. Try harder</item>
        <item>Stop drinking now. Food poisoning no fun</item>
        <item>You are cleverly disguised as responsible adult</item>
        <item>Tomorrow at breakfast, listen carefully: do what rice krispies tell you to</item>
        <item>Drive like hell, you will get there</item>
        <item>Wise person either need good manners or fast reflexes</item>
        <item>Practice safe eating. Always use condiments</item>
        <item> Hard work pay off in future. Laziness pay off now</item>
        <item>This fortune no good. Try another</item>
        <item>Of all 27 alternatives, running away is best</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>